In Particle University, India.
And today I'm going to talk about
the blurring of ontologies
through our analysis of marks Merinos
Living with, which was written
and crafted, published in 2012.
So the aim of the paper is to shed light
on the on the media specific metal itself
that is unique to the digital medium
and is facilitated once again.
On the eve of the paper, is to shed
light on media specific metal objects
that is unique to the digital medium
and is facilitated by the affordances
of that medium.
The paper begins with an overview
of the concept of metal apses,
and goes on to explain
how it is functional in the digital text,
through the manipulation of the various
multimedia elements of the text.
As a result of the interaction
of the reader with the metal tools
about which I'm going to talk in detail
in the presentation,
a certain
kind of immersive effect is induced.
And all these aspects,
such as metal immersion.
Are explored in this paper
in relation to the possible worlds theory
developed by Marie Laura Ryan and Alice
Bell in the context of digital literature.
For the analysis, the interactive fiction.
12 has been chosen.
So moving on to the major
theoretical framework of my paper,
it takes into account media
specific interactional metal, metal apses,
and digital occurrences that help in
achieving that metal effect through tools.
Then there is a motion reader
participation and possible worlds theory.
So introducing the author and the work.
Before I go into the discussion.
The contribution of marks
is quite significant in the field
of digital humanities for his produced
numerous electronic literature
pieces, short stories,
essays, nonfiction books,
and many more things.
Some of his creative digital works
have been mentioned in the Slide.
He's also the Director of Communication
of Electronic Literature Organization,
and a particular text
in discussion is created
using the Interactive Hypertext program,
and it was incorporated
in the Electronic Literature
Organization Volume 4 in 2022.
It talks about the ever shifting contents
of the living will of the narrator,
Millhouse,
who owns the company Druk Silver's.
Now, let me begin with the
discussion on metal
with an introduction to the concept.
It is an active device that that was
conceptualized by Gerard Senate in 2004.
In his work
Metallurgists from Figure to fiction,
which can be effectively utilized
in the framework of possible
worlds theory, which is originally defined
by Janet, is an intuition
by the narrator or narrative
into the universe or the inverse.
So metal is a kind of movement
between of entities,
between the distinct ontological realms.
So the theoretical idea has been developed
into distinct categories by different
theorists to specify how the movement is
marked across the ontological realms.
The idea of media specificity
of prime importance in the digital text,
as the medium, offers a set of affordances
that can be manipulated by the reader
in the.
Digital
literature and cannot be found in French,
and recognizing the importance
of the role of the medium, has posited
that the interactional metal induces
a special effect
based on the interaction
between the text and the reader.
However, he has introduced this
this term, but has developed on it
by talking about the blurring
of ontologies or the boundaries
between the ontologies have been blurred
through the readers virtual trees.
In the digital world.
This can be explained
through the exploration of the various
metallic tools that are evident
in the select piece, like the cursor,
the hyperlink,
or the second person addition.
So when we theorize
the cursor as a metal tool,
its significance as a commonplace
navigational tool employed in computer
games becomes all the more relevant.
For Ryan suggests
that the cursor on the screen
is the representation of the reader.
Is a virtual body in the virtual.
And additive as the son, the daughter,
the errand boy,
or the gardener is symbolized
on the screen in the form of the castle.
This is evidenced in the second clause,
where the narrator asks the reader
to reveal his his or her identity
to proceed with the narrative.
The relationship between the cursor
and the reader in the select text
is therefore ontologically significant
for its situation.
As a result of this,
the reader who is digitally manifested
as one of the four characters,
simultaneously executes
the textual possible
world of that character
according to possible worlds theory.
That actual possible world of a particular
character
is a combination of the different sub
words like the knowledge worlds, visuals,
obligation worlds, and various authors.
The entire narrative of Living
Well uses a hyperlink structure,
the manipulation of which is the story.
For instance, clicking on the link
of the Democratic Republic of Congo,
although one giving an idea of river
blindness, gives us examples of
extra textual details
that, given one standard of the text,
such links draw the reader
in a continuous cybernetic loop
of action and reaction,
and thereby reinforce immersion.
These links are used for a variety
of different functions in the text,
including establishing
the setting of the narrative
and giving the reader a sense
of the characters, personalities and feats
that the incur
as a result of their own choices.
So when the hyperlink is.
So here
the hyperlink is having an epistemological
and ontological function at the same time.
The effect of the second person
additions is such
that the reader is obliged to take up
one of the roles of the four inheritors
to allow narrative progression.
The entire narrative functions
in the form of a conversation,
and while the narrator speaks
through the narrative content,
the reader speaks through his clicks
that represent his choice of movement.
It is in this aspect
that a metallic exchange is manifested,
and if it's possible, textual worlds
are executed simultaneously.
For example, if we approach the text
through the role of the son Nigel,
the narrator expresses his frustrations
by directly rebuking the son
who is the reader, that is, the son
on the screen, and he, because he had
previously eloped for seeking his
responsibilities towards his sick father.
The son wished to have two parts
in the theater in the father's empire,
and dreamt of earning a fortune in UK,
never to set foot back in Congo.
As the narrator converses with the reader
as son, he is given certain.
Energy proceeds, so
to conclude the analysis
of three different kinds of
devices, like the cursor
or the metal hyperlink,
or the second person.
Narration
has shown that the affordances of the web
technology can produce
varying degrees of ontological violations.
Yet the discrepancy between
epistemological access
and ontological disparity
present through metallurgists highlights
the ontological ambiguous position
the leader
reader has in the text.
Simultaneously, the various textual worlds
of the colonial extortion
or for subjectivity
are also unfolded to the reader.
That is it. Thank you.
I stop sharing my stream.
I think everything was audible
because my internet was not proper.
So yeah, yeah,
it cuts out every once in a while, but